easy-birthday-cakes.com 2008-09-29

# Easy-Birthday-Cakes.com Privacy Policy

We recognize that your privacy is important. This document  
outlines the types of personal information we receive and  
collect when you use Easy-Birthday-Cakes.com, as well as some  
of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this  
will help you make an informed decision about sharing  
personal information with us.

Easy-Birthday-Cakes.com strives to maintain the highest  
standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our  
operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our  
customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy on our  
website.

Personal Information

Easy-Birthday-Cakes.com collects personally identifiable  
information from the visitors to our website only on a  
voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a  
voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email  
address, company name and telephone number.

This information is collected if you request information  
from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign  
up to join our email list or request some other service or  
information from us. The information collected is internally  
reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify  
our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries.

Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in  
our files. If we make material changes in the collection of  
personally identifiable information we will inform you by  
placing a notice on our site. Personal information received  
from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and  
will not be sold or provided to third parties.

IP Addresses IP addresses are used by your computer every   
time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a   
number that is used by computers on the network to identify   
your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by   
our web server as part of demographic and profile data known   
as traffic data so that data (such as the Web pages you request)   
can be sent to you.

Use of Cookies and Web Beacons

We may use cookies to help you personalize your online  
experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to  
your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to  
enable our systems to recognize your browser. The purpose of  
a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to  
a specific page. For example, if you personalize the sites  
pages, or register with any of our site's services, a cookie  
enables Easy-Birthday-Cakes.com to recall your specific  
information on subsequent visits.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by  
modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to  
decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the  
interactive features of the site.

A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor  
your journey around a single website or collection of sites.  
They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used  
by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic.  
They may be used in association with cookies to understand  
how visitors interact with the pages and content on the  
pages of a web site.

We may serve third party advertisements (such as, but not   
limited to Google Adsense) that use cookies and  
web beacons in the course of ads being served on our web  
site to collect information. 

Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify  
you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be  
used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions  
shouldn't cause a problem with our site, should you so  
choose.

Children's Online Privacy Protection Act

This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to  
children under the age of 13. We operate our site in  
compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection  
Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal  
information from anyone under 13 years of age.

Non-Personal Information

In some cases, we may collect information about you that is  
not personally identifiable. We use this information, which  
does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to  
administer the site, to track users' movements around the  
site and to gather demographic information about our user  
base as a whole.  The information collected is used solely  
for internal review and not shared with other organizations  
for commercial purposes.

Release of Information

If www.easy-birthday-cakes.com is sold, the information we have  
obtained from you through your voluntary participation in  
our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale  
in order that the service being provided to you may  
continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our  
website of that change in control and practices.

Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so,   
in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires  
it or for the protection of our legal rights. We may also disclose   
account information when we have reason to believe that disclosing   
this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action  
against someone who may be violating our Terms of Service or to   
protect the safety of our users and the Public.

How You Can Correct or Remove Information

We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our  
commitment to protect your personal information. If you have  
submitted personal information through our website and would  
like that information deleted from our records or would like  
to update or correct that information, please use our [Contact Us](http://www.easy-birthday-cakes.com/contact-us.html) page.

Updates and Effective Date

Easy-Birthday-Cakes.com reserves the right to make changes in  
this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy  
practices, we will post any changes here, so we encourage you to   
periodically review this policy so that you will know what information   
we collect and how we use it.  please be assured that if the Privacy Policy   
changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have   
submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially   
inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent 

Agreeing to Terms

If you do not agree to Easy-Birthday-Cakes.com Privacy  
Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use  
this site or any services offered by this site.

Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy  
policy.

You may contact Easy-Birthday-Cakes.com through our "[Contact Us](http://www.easy-birthday-cakes.com/contact-us.html)" form  
or you may send an e-mail to info [at] easy-birthday-cakes.com.

To contact Easy-Birthday-Cakes.com by mail, send correspondence to:

Attn:  Easy-Birthday-Cakes.com  
143 Boardman-Canfield Rd.  
# 114  
Boardman, OH  44512
